

# IT Vaardigheden

- C# Linq Design Patterns
- Databases SQL Typescript
- Javascript Angular
- Devops Jira Confluence
- Azure Pipelines Trello Miro
- Scrum Agile Kanban
- ASP.NET WEB API Razor
- .NET Core MVC REST DDD
- HTML PHP CSS

# **Taalkennis**

Uitstekend:

- Engels
- Nederlands

Goede basis (snel opgefrist)

- Spaans
- Frans
- Duits

## Soft-skills

- Absorberen van kennis
- Logisch denken
- Analytisch
- Teamwerk
- Empathie
- Assertief in omgang
- Verantwoordelijkheid opnemen

## Contact-info

Liefbilkstraat 11 - 9040 Gent 0484/62.39.97 dm.inbox@outlook.com https://dries-maes.github.io/

# **Dries Maes**

DEVELOPER

Na 3 jaar te werken als project manager in de publieke IT-sector was het duidelijk dat IT mijn toekomst werd. Ik herschoolde mij ging aan de slag als .NET C# ontwikkelaar waar ik snel doorgroeide tot product owner/manager. Mijn troeven: leergierig, makkelijk in omgang en neem verantwoordelijkheid op. Je kan rekenen op een bijzonder korte inlooptijd met een hoge mate van betrouwbaarheid en professionalisme. Ik ben heel breed inzetbaar en op zoek naar een lange termijn commitment.

## Loopbaansamenvatting

### Adjunct-diensthoofd ICT

Fonds Wetenschappelijk Onderzoek | 2022 tot heden

 Als adjunct diensthoofd sta ik voor een team van 14 developers en 2 IT medewerkers, verdeeld in 4 teams (3\*Scrum; 1\*Kanban). Naast mijn verantwoordelijkheden als leidinggevende vervul ik ook volgende rollen: Project manager, Project owner, Functioneel analyst, Business analyst, Facilitator, Devops engineer.

### C# .Net developer

Fonds Wetenschappelijk Onderzoek via DotNetLab | 2021 - 2022

• Developer voor .Net C# projecten, DDD architectuur & angular frontend, in een uitdagend traject waar we alle oude talen en structuren vernieuwen.

## Project manager (publieke sector)

CipalSchaubroeck NV | 2017 - 2019

• Project leider - Analyse, implementatie en migratie management.

#### Productbeheer (publieke sector)

Cevi NV | 2016 - 2017

 Als link tussen de ontwikkelaars en de klant was ik verantwoordelijk voor de analyses, offertes, opmaken van bestekken en de projectopvolging.

## **Opleidingsachtergrond**

#### .NET C# Developer

Obelisk & Dotnetacademy | 2020 - 2021

Een intensieve voltijdse opleiding van 9 maanden met de focus op .Net C#, gericht op de praktische vaardigheden die op de werkvloer verwacht worden.

#### Master in de bestuurskunde en publiek management

UGent - Grote onderscheiding | 2011 - 2016

De master in de bestuurskunde en publiek management vormt polyvalente mensen die de inzichten en vaardigheden hebben om in de hedendaagse publieke sector een modern bestuur te garanderen. De vier pijlers van de opleiding waren management, recht, economie en politicologie. (Ik was er voorzitter van de studentenraad, redacteur van de schoolkrant, lid van de faculteitsraad)



# **Dries Maes**

DEVELOPER

After working for 3 years as a project manager in the public IT sector, it was clear that IT was my future. I retrained myself and started working as a .NET C# developer where I quickly grew into product owner/manager. My qualities: eager to learn, easy to deal with and i can take responsibility. You can count on a very short run-in time and a high degree of reliability and professionalism. I am very versatile and looking for a long-term commitment.

## IT skills

- C# Ling Design Patterns
- Databases SQL Typescript
- Javascript Angular
- Devops Jira Confluence
- Azure Pipelines Trello Miro
- Scrum Agile Kanban
- ASP.NET WEB API Razor
- .NET Core MVC REST DDD
- HTML PHP CSS

## Languages

#### **Excellent:**

- English
- Dutch

The basis (quickly refreshed)

- Spanish
- French
- German

## Soft-skills

- Absorbing knowledge
- Logical thinking
- Analytical
- Teamwork
- Empathy
- Assertive
- Taking responsibility

## Contact-info

Liefbilkstraat 11 - 9040 Ghent 0484/62.39.97 dm.inbox@outlook.com https://dries-maes.github.io/

## Career summary

## **Deputy-director ICT**

The Research Foundation - Flanders | 2022 to present

 As deputy director I am responsible for a team of 14 developers and two analists/testers, divided into 4 teams (3\*Scrum; 1\*Kanban). In addition to my responsibilities as a manager, I also fulfill the following roles: Project manager, Project owner, Functional analyst, Business analyst, Facilitator, Devops engineer.

#### C# .Net developer

The Research Foundation - Flanders | 2021 - 2022

• Developer for .Net C# projects, DDD architecture & angular frontend, in a challenging process where we renew all old languages and structures.

## Project manager (publieke sector)

CipalSchaubroeck NV | 2017 - 2019

• Project manager- Analysis, implementation and migration management.

#### Product Owner (publieke sector)

Cevi NV | 2016 - 2017

 As the link between the developers and the customer, I was responsible for analyses, quotations, drawing up specifications and project follow-up.

# Educational background

#### .NET C# Developer

Obelisk & Dotnetacademy | 2020 - 2021

An intensive full-time training of 9 months with a focus on .Net C# & Angular, aimed at the practical skills expected in the workplace.

#### Master of Public Administration and Management

University of Ghent - Graduated with high honors | 2011 - 2016

The Master of Public Administration and Public Management forms polyvalent people who have the insights and skills to guarantee modern administration in today's public sector. The four pillars of the program were management, law, economics and political science. (I was president of the student council, editor of the school newspaper, member of the faculty council)